

CONTACT

- nicole.zimerman@gmail.com
- +54 1131796852
- Personal website
- 🟠 🛮 Almagro, Capital Federal, Arg
- github.com/nicolezimerman

TECHNOLOGIES

 Code languages: Javascript, Java, PHP, Html, SQL

• Libraries: ReactJs

• Frameworks: Laravel

Data bases: MySQL

• Issues trackers: Assembla, Jira

• Version controllers: Git

• Knowledge on: API Rest, MVC

model

• Plataform: Magento

LANGUAGES

English upper intermediate

Hebrew basic

EDUCATION

ASSOCIATE'S DEGREE IN SYSTEMS ANALYSIS

Institute of Technology ORT 2018 -2019

FASHION DESIGN

University of Buenos Aires 2013 -2017 (left)

HIGH SCHOOL
DIPLOMA WITH A
FOCUS ON COMPUTING
AND INFORMATICS

Technical school ORT 2008 -2012

NICOLE ZIMERMAN

Systems Analyst - Software developer

ABOUT ME

I'am a young professional experienced on technology projects working on this area for 5 years. One of my strengths is being able to adapt me quickly to the requirements, being flexible in my work and promote teamwork.

I'm looking for a place where I can grow my professional career, learn from my partners, improve my technical knowledge and orient my professional career towards frontend development.

I'm currently studying ReactJs on a online course.

EXPERIENCE

Java + ReactJS developer

GLAMIT | July 2020 - present

- Internal system development using Java for backend and ReactJs for frontend.
- Main tasks: Development an API using controllers and services layer for the business rules; Implementation of DAOs for access to DB information; Training new team members.
- Tools: Spring Framework; GIT; Jira to ticket tracking.

PHP backend developer

GLAMIT | January 2019 - June 2020

- Development of new functionalities on PHP, based on Magento ecommerce system.
- Internal systems development in PHP, using Laravel Framework.
- Responsible for bug fixes development and fulfillment of SLA requirements.
- MySQL database design.

Tester Analyst

GLAMIT | March 2018 - December 2018

- Execution of Test cases, and reporting bugs and incidents in the Assembla tracking tool.
- Documentation of new functionalities.
- Process data gathering in order to improve system, making proposals of new functionalities to be implemented.
- Communication with development and business teams.
- API REST test and use of system databases.

Youth Department Director

Centro comunitario Kadima | March 2017 - February 2018

- Coordination of community leaders and supervisors on non-formal education activities.
- Responsible for supervising educational project; leading the planification of projects for the entire department with the purpose of education and transmission of jewish and human values.

Tester QA

Truelogic Software | April 2015 - February 2017

- Development of test plans based on products requirements.
- Tasks: Test cases execution; tracking the results on the Jira tool. Bugs and incidents reporting. Cross browsing test and in multiple devices.
- Scrum methodology application.